Okay. Bye.
Everyone, stop what you're doing.
I have terrible news.
Dwight is
no longer with us.
What?
He's gone, damn it.
He's been promoted to
V.P. of Sabre Retail
and he's staying
in Florida forever.
So, he's alive?
Yeah. That was him on the phone.
He sounds wonderful.
Well, the way you said it made
it sound like he was dead.
How could I have
been more clear?
He had a massive
stroke of good fortune
and he is now in
a better place.
If Dwight's not coming back, does
that mean we can open his treasure?
You guys, we've gone over
this, there is no treasure.
When the team
left for Tallahassee,
Dwight told everyone
not to touch his treasure.
Don't touch my treasure.
Okay? You understand?
Obviously he wants us to obsess about it.
There's nothing in there.
Which is obviously what he
would want us to think,
making it the perfect
place to hide a treasure.
Oh, God, I'm Wallace Shawn
in The Princess Bride.
I think that Dwight
wanted us to realize
that this conversation among
friends is the true treasure.
No,no,no.
I am dying to
know what's in there.
Yeah, I know, Oscar. We all are.
But nobody's going to open it.
You'd have to be insane.
Hi. Hello.
Now carefully open the box.
It's a photo of all of us.
Oh, that's so sweet.
A dart?
Are you kidding me?
Who would put a poison dart... Well, I
mean, I don't know that it's poisoned.
I mean,
I just have to imagine.
God, I'm glad
he's okay though.
Kind of sounds
like he deserved it,
opening another man's
treasure and all. Wow!
Well, Mister Ball, it's been a pleasure.
Now, give my regards to hell!
All right!
Well swung by VIPVP.
I am loving the chemistry
between you two.
I am so happy Dwight is going
to be working alongside me.
We are a regular Archibald
and his man, George.
I bet. I'm excited.
Trick! There's no such thing.
It's not even a real English duo.
Ah!
I just made you look like the Goat of Dover.
And that doesn't exist either.
You think you're excited?
You should feel my nipples.
Pong!
Oh, that reminds me... Little
something from all of us.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you, Jim.
That's so thoughtful.
Fore! Oh, yeah!
He doesn't even care.
I don't even care!
This is the last time
I'll ever see Dwight.
It's a weird feeling.
It's, um...
What's the word?
It's not "bittersweet."
It's "sweet." Yeah.
Hey, man.
Selling cookies for Jada.
You want
the same as last year?
Would if I could
and I can so I will.
Put me down for one box. Don't care what it is.
Dealer's choice.
I'll put you down
for shortbreads.
Damn it.
Knock, knock. Hey.
It's Sasha's
first year in the troop
so I'm selling
cookies for her.
Anyway, would you
like some?
No. No.
What?
I've been selling here for five years.
This is my spot.
You can't claim territories. This is
the only place I interact with people.
Why can't you sell it
at your church or barbershop?
Or chess club?
You know what? It's your first
time, we'll split the office.
You can have Sales, the Annex,
Creed, and I don't know.
I'll just take Accounting.
That's it?
Yeah. Well, okay.
Thanks, Darryl.
Okay, great.
All I need is Kevin.
Dude buys more cookies
than everyone combined.
And then some.
When I first started selling cookies,
he was a relatively thin man.
Not a thin man, mind you.
Relatively thin.
Hey, Lucy, I'm home!
Babaloo.
Here, let me help.
I got it. It was so busy at the store today.
Really good cheese nibbles.
I had like a hundred.
Irene hired me as
her live-in helper.
We met at
the store launch.
I told her I was moving here
and I needed a place
and it just
sort of made sense.
I basically do
everything for her.
I run errands, I do
chores around the house.
I cook and clean.
Honestly, I don't know
how she survived without me.
When can I introduce you to my grandson?
He's a wonderful swimmer.
Shallow end, deep end.
He does it all.
Well, today might be
kind of tough, Irene.
I have to talk to
my old boss, Andy,
and tell him I'm
staying in Florida.
Oh! What kind
of tea is this?
Oh, I boiled some Gatorade.
Oh!
In England, they put the holes a
little bit to the right, you see.
We'll just chalk it up
to cultural bias.
If I may.
Try holding the putter, you
know, with your wrists here,
and your thumbs here.
Oh.
That's right.
Your little finger.
Would you like to
buy some cookies?
Cookies, eh?
Mmm-hmm.
Hmm.
Oh, the spring time
thinks that it's the best
And fall time
Cold time has
kind of a strut
And Valentine's
thinks that it's the best
But gather round, peeps
I'll tell you the truth
Nothing beats the cookie
season That's the truth
It's not
a scratch and sniff, Kev.
I know. But sometimes you
still get a little something.
Hey, you tricked me.
You just wanted Kevin.
You're new to the game.
You learned a lesson today.
See you next year, sport.
No, no, no, that's not fair. What if
Kevin wants to buy cookies from me?
I do.
See?
That doesn't mean anything. Kevin,
do you want to buy cookies from me?
Oh, I definitely do.
Huh. Hit the road, Jack.
No, you hit the road, Jack.
Hey, guys, come on.
Don't fight over me.
Why don't we split the order?
It's only fair.
No, wait, no. I'm buying.
I make the rules.
I actually do want
you to fight over me.
I want to be wined and
dined and sixty-nined.
Ugh!
Metaphorically sixty-nined.
Ew! Perverts.
No offense, Oscar.
Hop in! We have places to be!
No rest for the wicked.
All right,
so I guess this is it.
Well, Jim, I just want to say that
we haven't always gotten along.
And, at times, I've even
hated your guts, but...
Bye, bye. I win.
Good-bye, Dwight.
Robert! Race you to the clubhouse!
Gentleman's bet!
Whoo-hoo!
Well, he's
Florida's problem now.
Oh, let Dwight
have his fun.
Today will not be his day.
What's that?
I'm going to
tank the Sabre store
at the presentation
to the board.
I thought you
liked the store.
No, the store is lovely.
You created a wonderful space
to showcase our product line.
Great job. Cheers.
Thank you.
But there's a reason we sell our
products online and over the phone.
Have you ever used
Sabre electronics, Jim?
They're cheap,
they're unintuitive.
The Sabre store
would work
if we adopted
the carnival model
of leaving town once
everyone's wise to us.
Wow. When you put it that way, I
guess it does sound pretty terrible.
I couldn't just kill the project from the start.
Jo Bennett endorsed it.
Shame, though.
I did like Dwight.
Robert, I'm going to win! Ha-ha!
I'm the gentleman! Suck it!
Bravo, Dwight!
Very good!
Shame.
The math is simple, folks!
Deeper market penetration plus greater
visibility will raise Sabre...
To the power of two.
How did that look?
I'm not just
saying this,
that was the best
thing I've ever seen.
Told you.
When you guys do that whole
"power of two" shebang,
how about I pop up also?
I guess we'd have to
say "power of three."
Actually you know what?
Yeah, that actually works.
You'd spin off right,
I'd spin off...
You know what?
That is a great idea.
Cathy, write that down
and print it out.
It's going to make some
really good toilet paper.
All right.
There he is.
What are you doing here?
I thought I got rid of you.
Can I just talk to you
for one quick second?
What? Your stylist
ran out of messy spray?
Um, actually, it's for your own good.
I think we should...
You want to do
something for my own good?
Turn around,
walk out that door.
Do not stop until
you get to Scranton.
Find my cell phone charger, mail
it back to me and then go to hell.
Nice. Hey, Halpert, anyone ever tell
you, you look like Wooly Willy?
Silence.
I'm just trying to...
I know what
you're trying to do.
I don't want it.
But your face does look like
the guy from Operation.
It's the same guy.
That's the joke I made.
Different guy.
You know what...
I just think
you should know...
That you look like
the world's tallest hobbit.
Well, I tried. You saw it.
So, it's on the record.
I have a plane to catch.
Can you help me? I'm trying to
make a video chat with Andy.
Just open the program
and type in his username.
Can you just do it?
You type in your password.
Erin, one, two, three.
That's a terrible password.
And you don't
make a video chat.
You video chat.
All right.
Hello.
That's so weird. There's
something wrong with my laptop.
Oh.
I fixed it.
Now mine's broken.
Hang on.
Oh, there we go.
He said "I did like Dwight"?
He's going to fire him.
No,no,no,
I think it was more like,
"I liked him,
but I don't anymore
"because he did a bad job, so I'm
definitely going to yell at him."
Robert doesn't
talk like that.
You have to stop Dwight
from doing this.
I tried.
He will not listen.
Did you actually
try your hardest?
Yes. My pretty hardest.
Look, you haven't dealt with
him in a while, all right?
He's like Super Dwight.
It's like he's been bitten by a
radioactive Dwight or something.
Stanley, back me up.
Don't talk to me.
Stanley's very upset
that we're leaving Florida,
but he would back me up.
If Dwight's about to get
fired, you have to tell him.
Just get the words out,
that's all you can do.
Okay. All right.
What's a skinny guy like Toby
know about cookies?
You can't trust
him to understand
the wants and needs
of the thick man.
Maybe Toby from
two years ago.
Yeah.
That's true.
If I have a question about
my cookies at midnight,
who am I going to call?
Darryl. Toby's probably
in bed with some model.
Thank you.
I'm not going to comment
on my personal life.
Look, I need this. Okay, your
daughter is a pretty little girl.
Let her go door to door.
You think people are going to buy
cookies from my chubby daughter?
Ooh.
Baby, if you're watching this,
you're not chubby. You're beautiful.
Daddy's just got to
sell some cookies.
And we're also going to exercise more.
It's going to be fun.
Oh. You know what you
have to do to decide?
You need to make them do things
for you and buy you things.
Or have them sing that song that
the frog does in Looney Tunes.
Make them kiss each other.
Make them kiss me.
Ew!
Yes, this is, too, tan.
This right here.
No.
This is a tan spot.
I don't buy it. And that is a freckle.
That is not a tan, okay?
I'm going to have to inspect it
in person when you get back here.
I want you looking totally
Puertorriqueña when I see you.
Well, Andy,
I'm not coming back.
What?
I have a job here.
I work for an old lady.
Hello.
Andy?
Yeah, that's awesome.
That's great.
Oh, baby, telephone
And tell me I'm your own
Okay, this is tough
because Darryl,
you sang better and
you danced better,
but Toby has that indescribable
quality that makes a star.
I think I've
reached my decision.
I've decided that you guys are
going to keep doing things for me.
No,no,no,no.
It's not worth it.
No.
No, it's not worth it?
That's too bad.
Because I was feeling
particularly hungry this year.
Yeah, okay, so what?
You buy 40 boxes?
Hungrier
50?
You're not
talking triple digits?
Oh, yeah,
I'm talking triple digits.
Again.
Hello,
ma baby Hello, ma honey
Hello, ma ragtime gal
It's show time.
Dwight!
You again? Gosh, I keep throwing
you away, you keep flying back.
You're like
an Amish return stick.
Okay, great, listen, listen to me.
No,no,no,no.
Will you just let me
tell you one thing, please?
Yes, you may tell me one thing.
Great.
Wait, do you want to borrow money?
Listen to me.
Robert is going to
veto the Sabre store.
Jim, come on.
Dwight, he's going to kill the store.
Mmm-hmm.
And then I'm pretty sure
he's going to fire you for it.
Wait, he's going to kill the
store and he's going to fire me?
Yes.
That's two things.
Dwight, please.
Nice try, Jim.
Your pranks have
never worked in the past
and they're not
going to work today.
Okay, first of all,
they've mostly worked so...
You know what? You might
want to get to the airport.
It's going to take you a long
time to get through security
with all those beauty products.
Bye.
Dwight, come on.
Nothing is going to stop me.
That is the mark of a great man.
Unstoppability.
Dunder Mifflin, the farm, Mose, all those
things vanish in my rear view mirror.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I have a date with destiny.
And from what I hear
she's a...
Help! Help!
Gross, don't lick my hand. God,
why is there so much saliva?
All I had to do
was think about pie
and my salivary glands
did the rest.
Gross! What? What? What?
What?
Oh, God, Jim!
Oh! My appendix!
I'm sorry.
My wound hasn't healed yet.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, man. I'm so sorry. I forgot.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Where the hell is he?
I cannot do this without him.
I don't know.
He's not picking up.
Looks like
Shnoot's a no-show.
Guess he wasn't vice
prezzy material after all.
But I am.
Put me in, babe.
I've got the info down backwards,
forwards, and doggy style.
I'm your man.
Right.
Let's begin then.
Ladies and gentlemen,
allow me to introduce
the vice president of Sabre
Retail, Mister Todd Packer.
What's up?
What are you doing?
I'm just dealing
with Erin's stuff
since apparently
she's not coming back
and she didn't
bother to tell anyone.
We knew.
Ryan told us.
Ryan, why didn't you
tell me?
Thought you
checked my Tumblr.
You never update it.
Well, I updated it.
Does anyone else
think this is weird?
Like, kind of
uncool, actually?
To leave us without
a receptionist?
We'll find
another receptionist.
I mean, that's easy.
We'll be fine.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to...
Get up. Get up.
Okay. Okay.
All right? I'm not
going to let you by.
Then you know what? I'm going to
just have to run right through you.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Are you really revving up?
You know that doesn't work.
Jackie Chan!
Go.
Hi, this is Alex.
And this is Sam.
"Kevin can't come to the phone right
now because he's busy with us."
Perfect.
Now people will think I'm
doing hot girls all day.
I don't know, man. They might
think we're drag queens.
Yeah, I don't know why you picked
names that were also guys' names.
Okay, now who do I ride to
the kitchen like a pony?
Don't make me be
your pony, Kevin.
Forget it, man.
What do you mean?
I'm out. So is Toby.
This may be wrong,
but there's a limit
to what I will do
for my child.
Yeah.
I have my dignity, too.
I refuse to be
another man's horsey.
No, guys, stop! You have
to sell me cookies!
I'll do anything.
Hello, my
baby Hello, my honey
I'm even going
to kiss Meredith.
Mmm!
That's so good.
What are you doing?
No,no,no,no!
This ends now!
This is dangerous.
Thunder slam!
No!
Anything else you
need to talk about?
Nope. That was it.
Once again,
it's show time.
What baffles me is how you could
take a perfectly good idea,
which the great Jo Bennett
rightfully signed off on
and then, utterly
botch it in execution.
If I may speak to that,
I have only
been vice president
of this project for
the last half-hour,
so the man you want
is Dwight Schrute.
I don't see Dwight.
He clearly had
the infinite wisdom
to stay as far away from
this clown show as possible.
Whatever you do,
do not blame Todd Packer.
It is not his fault.
Blame his upbringing.
His parents.
The society that would mold
this idiotic creature.
Fire the employee, yes.
But not the man.
You may not
cancel his soul.
That was never
on the table.
Are you kidding?
She's the queen of the
whole frigging magilla.
And yet, Todd,
it's you who's fired.
Wait, I can't get fired.
I'm an institution.
I have been at this
company for 20 years.
How many of you have
been here that long? Huh?
Hey, hey, they're back.
Hi! Oh, my gosh!
Look at you guys.
Dwight, what are you
doing here?
I thought you were
supposed to be in Florida.
Yeah, the crazy thing
about that is, um...
Wow, you look great.
Did you lose some weight?
Thank you. For someone
who actually noticed this,
no, I didn't lose weight,
but I started using my makeup
to contour my face
to look skinnier.
I actually put on
five pounds.
Hey, good to
have you back.
Good to be back.
Hey, stranger.
Hey.
Oh, I missed you.
I missed you.
om
I'm going to Florida
to get Erin.
Forgot to turn off my email.
It's crazy, right?
It's just when she
said she was leaving,
I felt all... "You're
about to close four tabs,
"are you sure you
want to continue?"
Yes, I am sure.
Ah! Slow computer.